Say temptation, this sanitation decides whether the upper and lower bounds of a given function or algorithm
are the same.
So the average running time of an algorithm is always between the lower bound and the upper bound.
If the upper bound on notation and the lower bound is omega and notation give the same result, then
the thetan rotation will also have the same rate of growth.
OK, so the rate of growth is in the best case and the worst case are the same like f of an equals 10
and plus n as a result.
The average case will also be the same for a given algorithm or function.
If the rate of growth over the bounds for oil and omega are not the same, then the rate of growth of
the sedimentation will not be the same.
In this case, we need to consider all possible time complexities and take the average of those.
So the average time is that that annotation.
So if the upper and lower bound are the same, so average and the set then would be the same if lower
and upper bound are not the same.
We took the average time of all algorithm between them and consider them as if that that notation,
for example, of this we need to to get f of MN.
Half of an equal to any square over two minus.
And over to find that thatthat bound for that half of an.
If we have here.
This function, we have two terms, the first one and the second one we have and square over two and
the minus and over two.
So this function is between less than or equal that and the square.
And it is about a greater than.
Or equal to any square over five.
So for all and greater than to whatever and greater than to so.
And square over five less than or equal and square of a two minus and over two less than or equal to
any square.
In this case, the other an average notation is that the.
OK, so that that notation is set of and of squares and power.
Two, OK.
This is the third penetration, this is the average time between the upper bound and the lower bound,
and it's calculated according to the average algorithms, the time taken.